Kendal, you're showing a lot. What were
you hoping to show today at pro day? Uh
I just really just showcasing my route
running ability. That's what I do best.
Uh I'm fluid in in my routes. I'm a
smooth route runner. So, that's what I
came to do. Play football, put the
football onto the field. What are you
going to offer an NFL team? I'll offer
everything. The contesting catch, the
route running ability, the ability to
get open and create separation, and also
the blocking. I'm a willing blocker. I'm
physical. And I got the best mentality.
Now, obviously you guys have four guys
projected in the top 10. Maybe you're
going to be one of those guys at eight
for the Saints. I know you had some
contact with them. What's that contact
been like?
>> Oh, we we great guys. We Every time I
see coach Williams, we we laugh, we
joke, we have fun and stuff like that.
He told me he can He loved to coach me
if the opportunity comes. But yeah, only
God's plan that if all the cards fall
right, I'll be a Saint. Have you had a
chance to converse with Chris Olave or
any of those guys? Well, I I haven't
really talked too much about Chris
other than just like he's been wishing
me well. They just hope
we end up in St. Louis Not St. Louis,
the Saints together. So, yeah.
What's this process been like for you?
Because this is a long, tedious process
where, you know, sometimes you don't get
to work out as much as you want to. You
don't get to eat right all the time.
Yeah. So, the process been long and
hectic, especially because it's not
necessarily football. You
Um
you're training to test, like test well.
And then now I'm train I transition
after the combine, I transition to the
football side. So, it's just a It's a
lot right now. Just trying to stay in
football shape before OTAs come then.
Most importantly, just
trying to lift right now. I got the NFL
visits I'm going to all across the the
state, the country and stuff like that.
So, just trying to find as much time as
possible that I work out. Like I'm with
my strength staff right now. And we they
drew up a plan for me to work out in the
hotel and then just run outside the
hotel because that's all I got right
now. I'm not in too many I'm not in one
place for too long too long. Yeah. Is
there high expectations for the draft?
High anxiety? How's that going? Um
there's always high expectations. When
there's high expectations, you're doing
something right. So, I'm just blessed.
Like they say, pressure
pressure's a privilege. So, I'm just
blessed to be in this opportunity right
now. All right. Appreciate it. Thank
you.